Subs created by: David Coleman.
Morning, Mom.
Eh.
Tough night?
I had to get up three times with the baby
and your Father was absolutely no help.
Sure I was.
Flicking me in the forehead and
saying "baby's crying" is not helpful.
Honey, if I flicked you in the forehead and
didn't say anything, that'd just be mean.
Hey, after breakfast can somebody
watch Toby while I grab a quick shower?
Oh, I can't.
I have a maggot-infested rats'
nest that needs my attention.
- Bye.
Sorry, Mom. I'd love to, but
I'm going to the mall with Ivy.
We're gonna shop and look for jobs.
Mostly shop.
See you.
And I'm taking Charlie to the park.
Oh, maybe you can take Toby with you.
No thank you, Mama.
Hmm.
- Bye.
Gabe?
No thank you, Mama.
Today's all burnt toast
running late and Dad jokes.
"Has anybody seen my left shoe?"
I close my eyes, take a bite
grab a ride, laugh out loud.
There it is up on the roof.
I've been there, I survived.
So just take my advice.
Hang in there, baby
things are crazy.
But I know your future's bright.
Hang in there, baby.
There's no maybe everything
turns out all right.
Sure life is up and down.
But trust me, it comes back around.
You're gonna love who
you turn out to be.
Hang in there, baby.
Okay, Charlie. Here we go. Have fun.
Not too fast.
Not too fast. She's already
the fastest kid in the park.
If you want to see fast, you should
see my nephew Mason ride his trike.
He's so fast, he doesn't
have time to make friends.
Yeah, well, Charlie's so fast,
that.. That she makes friends,
but then she goes so far, by the time she
comes back they've changed and moved on.
And.. I am really not good at this.
The point is, Mason's faster.
No. Charlie's faster.
You know what this reminds me of?
The conversation that we
had before the baby race.
Oh. The baby race.
Come on, Charlie, you can do it.
Coming down the home stretch,
it's still Mason in the lead!
Come on, Charlie. It's now or never!
And the winner is Charlie!
Okay.
Charlie may be faster on
her feet, but on wheels?
Mason's the man.
Guess there's only one way to find out.
Are you saying what
I think you're saying?
Baby race two.
The empire trikes back!
Hey, Dad.
Hi, Mr. Wentz.
We're going to the mall
to shop and look for jobs..
But mostly shop.
- Wallet's over there.
- How much can I take?
Doesn't matter.
Nothing matters.
Ivy, why is your Dad so depressed?
I don't know.
I think it might be
something about his job.
- What does he do?
- I don't know.
Ivy, you're not going to the mall
without cleaning your room, are you?
Oh, Harry, honey. I don't
know why you're so down.
Show Teddy the award you got last night.
That's The Silver Plungie.
It's in recognition of Harry's 25
years in the plumbing supply business.
Oh, congratulations, Mr.
Wentz. That is quite an honor.
Well, I think so. It even
has an inscription. See?
It says, "to Harry Wentz,
for 25 years of duty".
Well, that's unfortunate.
Oh, I'm gonna go find a place for it.
Is this all I have to show..
For 25 years of my life?
A plunger that they
spray-painted silver.
It's glittery, too.
I used to have dreams.
Big dreams.
I wanted to be..
A weatherman.
I wanted to open a restaurant.
But..
I'm too old for any of that now.
Mr. Wentz, you are never too
old to pursue your dreams.
Oh, Teddy, I don't know.
Have you seen that commercial
for the new fitness centers?
The one with the talking gophers?
Right. The skinny gopher
says to the fat gopher..
"If you want to lose that weight, you
gotta get off your butt and 'gopher' it".
Sure, it's a terrific commercial.
But what's your point?
That's what you gotta do, Mr. Wentz.
You gotta follow your
dreams and "gopher" it!
"Gopher" it.
Why are you dressed like that?
Because I haven't had a
chance to do the laundry.
Believe it or not, this is
your shirt, your Dad's sweats,
and you don't even want to
know whose underwear I have on.
- They're PJ's.
- You don't know that.
I can see Batman's
head on the waistband.
What is that smell?
That's my new body spray.
Check it out.
"Duude".
With two "U"s.
Body spray for cool dudes ages 12 to 13.
What's all this about?
Nothing.
Oh, and by the way, for
the next couple of days,
I'm gonna be working on a project
with a kid from summer school.
Oh, I see. Is this kid
a boy kid or a girl kid?
I don't remember.
When I'm at school
I'm all about the work.
Aw.
My little baby has a crush.
Honey, can I give you some advice?
I'm 13 now. I don't need
any help from my Mommy.
That's a direct quote from
the "Duude" commercial.
Get out!
Okay.
I got all dressed up for nothing?
Hi, Gabe.
Hi, Jade.
I like hanging out at your house.
It's always so nice and peaceful.
You did what?! Without even asking me?
Harry, you come back here!
Girls, I have some exciting news.
Your Father quit his job, took our
life savings, and bought a restaurant.
I combined both my passions and created
the world's first weather-themed eatery.
Hurricane Harry's Weather Cafe.
And I owe it all to Teddy.
What did I do?
You did this.
And we're all gonna work there.
Me? What did I do?
Well, you wanted jobs? Now you got them.
- That's okay, Mr. Wentz..
- Oh, no, no, no, no, Teddy.
You are going to be a part of this, too.
Because of you, this family is
taking a ride on the crazy train.
All aboard.
Woo-woo.
Hmm.
Ah.
Okay.
Charlie, I've made some adjustments.
Your trike is now much more aerodynamic.
Where's my bell?
Oh, you don't need a bell,
you'll be in front the whole time.
Right?
Yes.
Well, well, well. You here to back out?
No, I'm here to show you a preview of what
you're gonna see tomorrow after the race.
My victory dance.
Uh! You like that?
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah.
Well, I got a victory dance, too.
- Where's it at?
- Goes a little something like this.
That's okay, you like this?
Oh, yes.
All right, everybody,
we open in five minutes.
Where's Mother nature?
Here I am.
Oh, Mary Lou, you look stunning.
Oh, you know what?
I thought this would be
silly, but I must say..
I do make it work.
All right, where are
my special waitresses?
Sunny and Cloudy?
Here we are.
So..
Kind of a bummer having to
go to summer school, right?
I like summer school.
Me too.
When I said bummer, I meant bummer!
You can't change the meaning of a
word by just saying it differently.
Bummer.
Um..
I'll be right back.
Hey.
How's it going out there, tiger?
Terrible. I keep saying the wrong thing.
Well.
I know how you can win her over
without saying a single word.
The baby? How is he gonna help me?
Once she sees how great
you are with Toby..
She is guaranteed to melt.
Now..
Hold him close.
Cradle the head.
I hope you're better with
girls than my older brother.
Jade, I don't think
you've met my baby brother.
This is Toby.
Oh my gosh, he's so cute.
And you're so good with him.
The trick is to cradle the head.
Here, have some more rain.
That's what we call water.
Isn't that fun?
Martin, party of four,
your table is ready.
This is Hurricane Harry
with a special bulletin.
The forecast for the next
few minutes is entertaining.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the musical stylings of..
Wentz's Weather Girls.
Hit it.
Hurricane Harry's is the
spot doo-dah, doo-dah.
We serve our dishes cold
and hot all the doo-dah day.
And night!
Wentz's Weather Girls.
And they'll be back to do it
again every hour on the hour.
I liked it better when I
didn't know what my Dad did.
Think we're dry enough to go in yet?
Nope.
Still squishing.
Hey.
What hit us during that
last storm? Was that sleet?
No. Kid threw a bowl
of nachos into the fan.
We gotta quit this job.
We can't. Your Mom would kill
me and your Dad would be crushed.
Well, if he adds an earthquake
tomorrow, we might actually be crushed.
Wait, we can't quit.
But we could get fired.
Yeah.
Ooh, I don't know what you're
thinking, but I like it.
Hey, do you mind if we
take a break for a second?
Why?
There's just this thing
I do for my baby brother.
I share life lessons
and give him advice.
I call it a video diary.
That is the sweetest thing ever.
I get that a lot.
Hey, char..
Toby.
It's your big brother Gabe here with
another one of my signature video diaries.
Anyway, last night after I tucked
you in and kissed you on your head,
I sang you to sleep with a song.
Oh, can you sing it now?
Please?
Um.
Hush, little Toby go to sleep.
You're already asleep
so stay asleep.
La-la-la la-la-la la-la-la.
Sleep.
Sleepy sleep, sleepy
sleep sleep, sleep, sleep.
Aw.
Well, that's all for
now, so, I'll just say..
Good..
Fortune, Toby.
That's sort of my trademark.
Now, remember, Charlie.
Winning isn't everything.
- It's the only thing.
- Yes. Yes.
Okay, you know that shame you
felt for the last two years?
It ends today.
Or it could get worse
depending on how this goes.
Okay.
The race is to that lamppost and back.
First trike to cross
the finish line wins.
Wins what?
- Hey, Dad.
- What is going on?
Nothing.
We're just hanging out at the park.
Then why have the kids
got numbers on them?
Because we're teaching
them their ones and twos.
How many times have we been over this?
You cannot race children like horses.
Can we race them like dogs?
You can't race them at all.
All right, kids, come on. Hey,
who wants to go to the playground?
Huh? Okay, come on.
Man!
I was all fired up for a race today.
Yeah, me too.
You know, we could still have a race.
Where's Toby?
Dad took him to the park.
What?
No, no, Jade's about to leave
and I need to make a move.
So make your move.
I don't have a move.
I need Toby.. She likes it
when I do nice things for him.
Gabe, I'm leaving.
Wait!
Hey.
So..
Um..
Uh..
I was just wondering if..
You wanted to go to a
movie with me sometime?
Oh..
Um..
No, thank you.
But I thought you were kinda into me?
Yeah, as a friend but..
I could never date you.
I like bad boys.
Wha.. But I am a bad boy.
I was just kidding about
all that baby stuff.
Gabe, be proud of who you are.
A sweet, sensitive, good boy.
No. I'm not. I'm a
total jerk, ask anyone.
Sweetie-pie.
This blanket you knit for the baby is..
Absolutely precious.
Bye, Gabe.
Whoa!
Woo! Yes! Yes!
Watch this!
Well, that brings us to the top of
the hour which means that it's time
to give it up again for
Wentz's Weather Girls.
You ready to get fired?
Hit it.
I guess that was a bad idea.
We've ruined everything.
If you have to make some
tough choices, we understand.
And I'm talking about firing us.
That was..
Awesome!
My weather girls.
We are going to be together forever.
Well, what do you know.
My boys.
Yeah.
He woke up from his nap
so we're just hanging out.
Oh.
You know who Toby reminds me of?
You.
Because he doesn't have a girlfriend?
No.
Because you both have
that sparkle in your eyes.
And that's another thing girls like..
A sparkle.
Thanks, Mom.
Well, since you're watching Toby, you
don't, um, mind if I take a nap, do you?
Well, I.. I guess, but if he..
Mom?
Hey, Toby. Gabe here.
So, I want to tell you everything
that I've learned about girls.
That's it.
Anyway, if you ever need
any advice in the future..
Wait. What.. What are you doing?
Making a video diary for Toby.
Wha.. That's kind of my thing.
Not any more.
So..
The next time I have a crush on a
girl, wish me good fortune, Toby.
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
Jealous?
What? No. Confused. What does
"good fortune, Toby" even mean?
It means that Toby has the good fortune
not to hear "good luck, Charlie".
Okay, give me my camera.
Good fortune, Toby.
Good luck, Charlie.
Woo. What a ride.
You know, after a workout like that,
I don't want some kind
of kiddie bubble bath.
I'm 12 to 13 now.
I want a body spray that
works as hard as I do.
That's why I use "Duude".
Duude, when you don't need
help from your Mommy any more.
Duude, from the makers
of "Guy" and "Bro".
Subs created by: David Coleman.